Release group MANIA presents
http://doramamania.mybb.ru
http://vk.com/doramamania
Project coordinator and song translator: Nemie
Final episode
Translators: Nemie, Kaia, tamaramin
Beta Editor: Sana
Will you hear him?
The same voice that is in such a hurry to confess
I'll show you something good as a gift
Are you still listening?
Can you hear my heart?
How raindrops settled on the window
Also my mind is consumed by you
Need you
The Emperor forbade us to hold an official ceremony
I miss you
But I secretly prepared something
Are you upset?
That's more than enough
Don't worry
I just wanted to get you out of the palace
Even though we are married, I will consider us friends
I'm not worried about that
It will be quiet and cozy in these chambers,
because they are located far from the main house
My house is nearby, come whenever you want
Oh, and also this...
Thanks for saying you want this
Will you hear him?
The same voice that is in such a hurry to confess
Are you still listening?
Can you hear my heart?
How raindrops settled on the window
Also my mind is consumed by you
It happened that I would reach the very sources of the stream,
Sitting down, I contemplate how the clouds rise in the distance
Need you
I miss you
Damn!
Wow, practicing your sword skills again?
I thought you were good at it
Here. Let's see how kind you are to your husband
Okay, that's enough, let's go inside.
The court physician leaves his position,
I asked him to stop by on his way home
Doctor?
But I'm fine
You've suffered a lot, so you need a healer
Let's go
Until the time you left the palace, I did not feel the child's pulse
- But now...
- It was too early
You wouldn't know
Child? So you're saying...
As I said earlier,
your heartbeat is palpitating, your health is not good
Because of the child you have become weaker
If you insist on keeping the child...
It's okay
If the child is safe, nothing else matters.
Why do you say that?!
You have to keep it a secret
Please delay your return and stay here for a while.
Okay
Lady, you shouldn't stand in the cold wind
You should stay in bed
Baek Ah said that their marriage is just a formality
However...
look at this
"The 14th Prince's wife watched as
how the prince trained with the sword for a long time"
"They held hands and took care of each other"!
Your Majesty, don't you know Miss Su?
She was friends with Jeong when she was young
It has many striking features
She communicates equally with both men and women
Su!
Why did you come here?
Cold wind can harm your baby
Get up
She asked me not to worry and sleep peacefully
This is the first time I've slept in the same room as my wife.
Why are you pushing me?
Now when I look at you, I see that you and I have matured
A lot of time has passed
There are good times and there are bad times
So many days have passed
I've been old enough to understand this
Do you remember our first meeting?
Was this in the 8th Prince's library?
Or when I saved you?
Are you talking about when you came running to me with a stick?
I was shocked then
I've never seen such a brave girl
And when did you fight with Eun?
I always laugh when I think about it
Your head was a complete mess, and Eun had a bruise on his face
-You were full of energy
- Was
Why didn't you keep your promise that you would sing for my birthday?
- I waited every year
- Lord
Okay, I'll sing this year
Do you remember?
You snuck into the bathhouse and spied on us
Why did you do this?
If you think about it, you were cunning even at that age
It's not fair
I was so surprised that I didn't see anything
Don't lie! You saw everything, right?
I really didn't see
No, what's wrong with my body?
I'm still looking at you from the outside
From now on, I am no longer interested in news about Jeong and Hae Soo
It seemed to me that you are my love
Make sure I don't hear from them again
I kept thinking that you feel the same way
Although you look the other way
Like the wind, like dust
I can't catch you and see you
Finally, it's just the two of us left here.
Do you remember: I love, I love
You and me
just you and me
I believe there was love, I’ll call it fate
Now I can forget about truth and lies
misunderstanding and jealousy,
Do you remember: I love, I love
dangerous struggle for the throne and death
Now I can devote my time
In your eyes, I settled in your gaze
love for you
And I can only answer you:
Hold me if I'm swinging
my love
In about six months
What's wrong with my wife? Why did she give birth so early?
After all, your daughter was born healthy
She is very beautiful
The child was stillborn
Do you understand?
Take her to the nurse
You gotta watch your words
Don't worry about the baby
She is very beautiful and healthy.
Heaven blessed her
I'll find her the best nurse in the area.
What a joy
So stop worrying about the baby, think about yourself.
You must definitely restore your health
I have a favor to ask
to His Majesty
Do you want to show the child to the emperor?
I...
I want to see him
Okay
Send this to the emperor.
Let him read it as soon as possible
Okay
Stop!
My wife's handwriting is like the emperor's
It will look weird
The distribution of rice to clans should be modified
If someone has less,
they will be weaker
Everything the clans have
- land and slaves
Your Majesty, the 14th Prince has sent you a letter
He never tires of writing letters
You won't read it?
I'm sure he has a lot of resentment towards me
I don't want to read it and be upset
He said he had a message for you
I even sent someone
Do I look like the type of person who has time for meetings?
Forgive me
Has he arrived yet?
I wrote so many letters...
Does he hate me that much?
Send someone else
If you give him my message, he will come
I did it, but...
Yes, I forgot. I'll send someone else
Let's go out. You have to feel happy to get better.
I brought the most famous musicians from Songak
And captured the peonies
Don't you want to see them?
Peonies?
Is there a song you'd like to hear?
Play your best song
One courtier was the emperor's lover
They say this song made him fall in love with her
Emperor?
I want to listen
I love you
Once upon a time
you promised that you would treat my life as your own
Remember this?
My daughter...
protect her
instead of me
You can't let her go to the palace
Why do you say such things?
He won't come
Su
The flower will fall to the ground, it withered
In the next life
you will remember me, right?
I will forget you
He will be all alone, so sad
I want to forget everything
Even in my dreams...
I want to forget
The sky will lose its stars, it will instantly become sad
And suddenly it starts crying like a little rain
It feels like a flower blooms and then withers
If so, come back
Su...
didn't hate me that much...
Apparently she sent you letters
Haven't you read them?
Our life is like a dream
Right and wrong. Love and hate
All this dies over time, quietly disappears without a trace.
Are you still angry about love and holding grudges?
I was constantly worried
that I could leave you with hatred instead of love,
not allowing you to rest
I still love you
When you gave up everything and stood next to me in the rain...
When you shielded me with your body from a flying arrow...
I can never forget you
The opposite of love is not hate
It's giving up on someone
I was afraid you'd think
that I abandoned you,
so you give up on me
I missed you so much...
but I couldn't be there
I hope one day we meet again in the garden
I will wait for you every day
Su!
Where is Su? Where is she?!
Su...
Stop playing around and come out. Su...
Su! Where are you?
Where are you?!
Su! Su!
What have you been doing all this time?
Don't pretend you're sad
You brought it to this
Your name was written on the envelopes!
I didn't know there were letters from Su inside!
I did this because you and her have similar handwriting
But you should have known that Su was dying
I know you have someone who has been following us!
You shared the same chambers and got along well
He stopped giving reports about you
Su... let's go
Let's go
No you can't! No way! She is my wife!!!
Out of the way
Su may be dead, but she's my person
Jeong, you should know! Better than anyone!
Do you know who Su would like to be with?
If you really consider Su a friend, stop fighting the emperor.
Hae Soo spent her life stuck among us
She couldn't afford a lot of things
Still... do you want to make her even sadder?
Are you...
Su
How stupid
I hide my tears deep inside
I want to forget everything about you
It's time for us to leave the fate that brought us together
Even though we will have to live in tears
I'm not alone so I'm okay
You are here, Your Highness, so why am I alone?
As if a free wind will carry you away
I kept looking for the way to you, but I never found it
I won't leave
I couldn’t catch the fate that was moving away from me
So I'll let you go completely
I won't leave
Let me in!
I am the one who could be the emperor!
If you want to kill me, then hang me in front of Jeongdeokjeong!
Are you asking me to kill myself?
What?
The Emperor sent to see if I was dead or not?
I came to deliver something
Hae Soo asked for this
She died a long time ago
She asked me to give you a letter from Chae Ryung
There's nothing more I can do for you
Sorry
I know the end is near
But this chance...
May I come with you, your highness?
I don't know when else I'll get the chance to leave the palace.
I’m just such a person - if I fall in love, I can’t stop loving
That's how stupid it is
Chae Ryung has no regrets
I'm not mad at anyone
Is there any point in what we are doing...
Only we ourselves can answer
Silly
Why don't you hate me?
Why?
Prince Wang Won was sentenced to death for treason
My father will catch you
You're Uka's daughter, right?
I'm your uncle, your 13th uncle
Liar. You look like a street musician
I'm telling the truth
What's your name?
Name? Bok Soon
What's your name? Zhong Ziqi?
- Bok Soon
- Wu Hee!
It's time for us to go to our rooms!
Yes, okay
Bok... Sun?
Because I'm next to you, I'm very happy
Because I'm next to you, I keep dreaming
Because I'm next to you, I smile so brightly
Is this the talisman of the seven stars of the Big Dipper?
Where did you get it?
I don't know.
He was always with me
For you to be mine, I always pray to the Gods
My favorite thing
If you see my love and my feelings
If you find my love and the path to me
I will give my heart completely
Right now I really want to not be associated with Hubaekje
If you can stay with me for the rest of your life
I am yours with all my heart
I'm with you
All with you
I heard you still have no plans to get married, you spend your time in the fields
If there were no worries, how boring would life be?
The Emperor spends his time reading "Fundamentals of Politics in the Zhenguan Era"
Now he's using his sword
He frees the slaves and returns their titles and titles
Takes power from powerful clans
You are still interested in what is happening in the palace, as usual
I'm just watching
This is So
It's interesting to see what kind of emperor he became
Interesting...
maybe Goryeo rules now
strongest emperor in history
He had to try hard
Recently...
I realized that there are faces that cannot be forgotten
Do you still miss Hae Soo?
Who knows
I've always... given my heart
I've made a lot of mistakes in my life
Only now I realized it
Today is his birthday...
How can you never go to Zhu?
It will be enough if you just visit him
He's afraid of his own father
You treat him as your opponent, Your Majesty
You have already gotten rid of your nephews Gyeongchongwon and Heunghwagun...
At least trust your son
Listen, Empress
I see right through people who hide their true selves under invisible masks.
Both you and this child...
I know very well that one day you will reach me
So... you still only remember her?
Hae Soo was the only one who said that we are all equal
You freed the slaves because you can't forget her
Did you think I didn't know?
Let's assume that's the case
But even if you know it
will something change?
Now that I think about it, I understand why Hae Soo left.
I know the reason
Dad!
Don't run, you'll hurt yourself!
You crashed into me
Who do we have here?
Dad!
Hello Your Majesty
You shouldn't leave Jeongju, but you came to the palace?
Today is the anniversary of Su...
Forgive me
For a second I lost my mind, this won't happen again
Is she your daughter?
Yes
Your family asked for permission to marry you, I decided to give consent
However...
your daughter is old enough
How old is she?
I'm sure you're busy with government affairs
Why do you care about my child?
Come with me
Stop
Leave the child
I can't unless you kill me
Really?
This child...
She asked that the girl not live in the palace
It's very scary and lonely there
She said she didn't want that fate for her.
Hae Soo cared only about this until her death
14th Prince, Wang Jong
Your link has expired
I wish you could go to the palace right now
Do you want to leave that bad?
Yes
I can't help but think about him
You promised me something else
He said that you will only be the emperor's man, no one else
Yes
However, I think there was only one emperor for me
He was a brother and friend to me
and ruler
Speaking of Ms. Hae Soo, I don't think she was from this world
If you think back to the past, you remember many examples
So you should forget her
If you think about a person you can't reach, you'll end up like me
Have you seen it?
Then...should I call you "my man"?
You are my only empress
What is this again?
Seriously, who is he to make me cry again?
Goryeo Era Makeup Art
Buddhism influenced Goryeo
people began to wash their eyes and take baths
Bath products and cosmetics began to appear during this era
Writer Seo Kun from the Song Empire traveled to Goryeo, after which he reflected in his book...
I had the same dream for a year
A man with a long scar on his face
He hid it with a mask, like this
He was dressed in ancient robes
It's because you escaped death
You almost drowned, and when you were rescued, you came to your senses only a year later
I'm fine now
I don't know why I dreamed about him
I cried so much
The ingredients were ground into powder,
to make something like a face mask
They could go to the market
to buy things from Bulgaria
Bulgarian roses were sold there
The amazing thing was that they created cosmetics from these flowers
Hello
Go Ha Jin
- Your surname is Guo?
- What?
Yes, yes, my name is Go Ha Jin
Did you know that during Goryeo times, Go's last name was pronounced Hae?
How's that?
We just sell cosmetics from the Goryeo era.
Funny coincidence
Accidents are not accidental
Everything just goes back to normal
What?
The smell of roses is so strong in here
And, our products contain a lot of rose oil
Especially in this serum
It is made using Bulgarian rose oil and Houttuynia cordata extract.
This is Bulgarian rose oil.
You didn't use it, did you?
-Are you okay?
- What?
Nothing like that
If used regularly,
the skin will be in excellent condition
Did you know that during the Goryeo era
Was there something like a BB cream?
Men use it a lot these days...
So now get ready
I'll never let you go
I think you need to rest
What's wrong with me?
You better leave.
Don't worry and go home
I'll change the menu
Sorry
Paintings from the Goryeo era
Grab them immediately!
Gwangjong?
It wasn't a dream
This is not a dream
You are so generous, Your Majesty!
Don't worry, I'll save you
Wow! Will you enjoy it alone, brother?
She's mine.
This girl belongs to me
So now get ready
I'll never let you go
The moment you touched my face,
I decided never to let you go
His name was So
...the liberation of slaves enslaved during conflicts between warring clans...
Gwangjong was a fair and wise emperor
...deep feeling of guilt...
Now you won't be recorded
in history as a "bloody ruler"
I will help you
The flower will fall to the ground, it withered
He will be all alone, so sad
The sky will lose its stars, it will instantly become sad
I'm sorry
Sorry for leaving you alone
And suddenly it starts crying like a little rain
It feels like a flower blooms and then withers
Sorry...
Tell me with the wind, please
Our 8th brother...
passed away
I have no one else to see, so I'll leave again
With the appearance of snow, all dreams will come true
Take care of yourself
With all my heart I believe so, they are sincere
Do you know my heart that it always waits like this?
If so, come back
Life is fleeting
Emperor Taejo's last words were that life is fleeting.
She's fragile and vain
He said life is so short
But I think he was wrong
You and I are together
so how can it be in vain?
When I see you I
I can’t breathe, I’m timid
It's as if everything in the world has stopped
I always get nervous when you get that look on your face.
If I pass by like a breeze,
I feel like you're going to leave me and go away
you won't even notice
What are you afraid of? What are you hiding?
My heart is all given to you
Just...
But loving you is very painful for me
Living here I worry every day
And so sad
Every step I take...
I need to cross you out of my heart
I feel like I should be careful
It's like I'm walking on thin ice
so hard
Sometimes I feel like I can't breathe
Even if you have me?
Don't forget, please!
Do you still feel that way?
That eternal love of mine
If we met in another world and at another time...
I thought about how wonderful it would be
By the will of fate
If only this were possible...
Suddenly I will be able to meet you!
I wouldn't be afraid of anything
I could openly...
All I wanted was to love you freely
And it’s still just as difficult for me to forget you
It's so hard for me
This dream is bad, when I remember, I cry
always
I believe once upon a time
how I want to love
I can
If we are from different worlds...
I will find you
My... Su
My knee hurts a little
Another place and another time here, but I believe, you are my love
Come on, get on your back
Get up!
It's okay
A fair wind will bring your scent, it’s so easy for me to recognize it
But I don't understand
Let's go!
- Let's begin!
- Okay
When did you settle in my heart, tell me
- Let's run!
- Forward!
I don't understand
Thanks for watching with us!
Release group MANIA
http://doramamania.mybb.ru
http://vk.com/doramamania
Why is my heart beating fast?
You may suddenly pass by and not notice, have you forgotten me?
But until you remember me, I will wait for you
And you're on me...